<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Quran Explorer on cmdragon's Blog</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/Quran-Explorer/</link><description>Recent content in Quran Explorer on cmdragon's Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/Quran-Explorer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quran Explorer - Gratis tool voor Arabische analyse van het Koran, met drie stappen voor diepe tekstverheldering en overwinnings van taalbarrières</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/nl/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/nl/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>Quran Explorer is een gratis tool voor de Arabische analyse van het Koran, speciaal ontwikkeld om taalbarrières voor niet-moedertaalsprekers te overwinnen. De tool ondersteunt diepe tekstverheldering (met woordbetekenis, grammatica en achtergrond), meertalige vergelijking, audiosupport en notitiefunctie. Gebruikers kunnen met drie eenvoudige stappen gratis gebruik maken tekst lokaliseren, analyse verkrijgen en delen opslaan, waardoor het leren van het Koran voor iedereen toegankelijk wordt.</description></item><item><title>Quran Explorer - Strumento gratuito di analisi araba del Corano, decodifica approfondita in tre passaggi per superare agevolmente le barriere linguistiche</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/it/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/it/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>Quran Explorer è uno strumento gratuito di analisi araba del Corano, progettato per risolvere le barriere linguistiche nell&amp;rsquo;apprendimento dei testi sacri da parte di non madrelingua. Supporta l&amp;rsquo;analisi approfondita dei testi (vocabulary, grammatica, contesto), il confronto multilingua, l&amp;rsquo;audio ausiliario e la funzione di note, consentendo a ogni utente di utilizzarlo gratuitamente in tre semplici passaggi individuare il testo, ottenere l&amp;rsquo;analisi e salvare/condividere, per facilitare un apprendimento accessibile a tutti.</description></item><item><title>quran explorer - Ücretsiz Kur'an Arapça Çözümleme Aracı, 3 Adımda Derin Metin Analizi, Dil Engellerini Kolay Aşma</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tr/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tr/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>quran explorer, ana dili Arapça olmayanlar için Kur&amp;rsquo;an metinlerinin dil engellerini aşmak amacıyla tasarlanmış ücretsiz bir Arapça çözümleme aracıdır. Kelime, dilbilgisi ve bağlam analizi gibi derin metin çözümlemesi, çoklu dil karşılaştırma, ses desteği ve not alma fonksiyonlarını sunar. Kullanıcılar metni konumlandırarak, çözümlemeyi alarak ve kaydederek paylaşarak ücretsiz olarak kullanabilir; bu da öğrenmeyi sıfır engelli hale getirir.</description></item><item><title>quran explorer - Δωρεάν εργαλείο ανάλυσης Αραβικής Κοράνιο, βαθιά αποσύνθεση στα αγία κείμενα με τρία βήματα, εύκολη υπέρβαση της γλωσσικής εμποδισμού</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/el/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/el/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>Το quran explorer είναι ένα δωρεάν εργαλείο ανάλυσης Αραβικής Κοράνιο, σχεδιασμένο για την επίλυση των γλωσσικών εμποδίων των μη μητρικών ομιλητών κατά τη μελέτη των αγίων κειμένων. Υποστηρίζει βαθιά ανάλυση των κειμένων (συμπεριλαμβανομένων λεξιλογίου, γραμματικής, πλαισίου), σύγκριση πολλών γλωσσών, ηχητική βοήθεια και λειτουργία σημειώσεων. Με τρία απλά βήματα (προσδιορισμός κειμένου, λήψη ανάλυσης, αποθήκευση/μεταβίβαση) ο χρήστης μπορεί να το χρησιμοποιήσει δωρεάν, βοηθώντας στην επίτευξη μηδενικού φραγμού μάθησης.</description></item><item><title>quran explorer - أداة مجانية لتحليل القرآن الكريم بالعربية، تحليل متعمق لآيات القرآن في ثلاث خطوات، تجاوز عوائق اللغة بسهولة</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ar/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ar/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>quran explorer هي أداة مجانية لتحليل القرآن الكريم بالعربية، مصممة خصيصًا لحل عوائق اللغة التي تواجه غير الناطقين بالعربية الأصلية عند دراسة الآيات. تدعم التحليل المتعمق للآيات (بما في ذلك المفردات والقواعد والخلفية التاريخية)، والمقارنة متعددة اللغات، والدعم الصوتي، ووظيفة الملاحظات. يكفي للمستخدم تحديد الآية، والحصول على التحليل، وحفظها أو مشاركتها في ثلاث خطوات فقط، مما يسهل التعلم دون عوائق.</description></item><item><title>quran explorer - 무료 코란 아라비아어 해석 도구, 3단계로 심층 분석으로 언어 장벽 극복</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ko/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ko/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>quran explorer는 비모국어 학습자가 코란 아라비아어 경문의 언어 장벽을 극복할 수 있도록 설계된 무료 해석 도구입니다. 단어, 문법, 배경을 포함한 심층 해석, 다국어 대조, 음성 보조, 노트 기능을 지원하며, 경문 위치 지정, 해석 얻기, 저장 및 공유 3단계로 무료로 사용 가능하여 입문 장벽을 낮춥니다.</description></item><item><title>quran explorer - 無料のコーランアラビア語解析ツール、3ステップで深層構造を解明し、言語障壁を突破</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ja/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ja/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>quran explorerは、非アラビア語話者向けに設計された無料のコーランアラビア語解析ツールです。単語・文法・背景を含む深層解析、多言語対照、音声補助、ノート機能を備え、経文の位置指定・解析取得・保存共有の3ステップで無料で利用可能。言語障壁を克服し、誰もが学びやすい仕組みを実現しています。</description></item><item><title>Quran Explorer – Ferramenta gratuita de análise árabe do Alcorão, desconstrução profunda em três passos para superar barreiras linguísticas</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>O Quran Explorer é uma ferramenta gratuita de análise em árabe do Alcorão, concebida para resolver barreiras linguísticas no estudo de versos por não falantes nativos. Oferece análise aprofundada (vocabulário, gramática, contexto), comparação multilíngue, suporte com áudio e funcionalidade de anotações. Com apenas três passos – localizar versos, obter análise e salvar/compartilhar – usuários podem usar gratuitamente, facilitando o acesso ao aprendizado sem barreiras.</description></item><item><title>Quran Explorer – Free Arabic Quran Analysis Tool, Three-Step Deep Deconstruction of Verses, Effortlessly Overcome Language Barriers</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>Quran Explorer is a free Arabic Quran analysis tool designed to overcome language barriers for non-native learners. It offers deep verse analysis (including vocabulary, grammar, and historical context), multi-language comparison, audio assistance, and note-taking features. Users can access it in three simple steps locate verses, obtain analysis, and save/share—enabling barrier-free learning.</description></item><item><title>Quran Explorer – Kostenloses arabisch-grammatische Analysetool für den Koran Dreistufige Tiefeanalyse, leicht überwindung der Sprachbarriere</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/de/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/de/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>Quran Explorer ist ein kostenloses arabisch-grammatisches Analysetool für den Koran, speziell entwickelt, um die sprachlichen Hürden für Nicht-Muttersprachler beim Lernen der Textstellen zu überwinden. Es bietet tiefgehende Textanalyse (inklusive Vokabeln, Grammatik, Kontext), mehrsprachige Kontraste, Audiounterstützung und Notizfunktion. Nutzer können durch die drei Schritte „Textstelle lokalisieren, Analyse erhalten, Ergebnisse speichern“ kostenlos loslegen und so barrierefreies Lernen ermöglichen.</description></item><item><title>Quran Explorer – nemokama „Korano“ arabų kalbos analizės įrankis, trys žingsniai gilios teksto analizės, lengva kalbos barjero įveikimo</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/lt/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/lt/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>Quran Explorer yra nemokama „Korano“ arabų kalbos analizės įrankis, sukurtas siekiant išspręsti nežinomos kalbos mokymosi barjerą. Įrankis pateikia gilų tekstą (įskaitant žodžius, gramatiką, kontekstą), daugia kalbės palyginimą, garsinę pagalbą ir mokymosi užrašų funkciją. Vartotojai lengvai naudojasi įrankiu per tris žingsnius nustatyti tekstą, gauti analizę ir išsaugoti bei dalintis, užtikrindami lengvą ir nekliudomą mokymąsi.</description></item><item><title>Quran Explorer – Outil gratuit d'analyse arabe du Coran, décortiquer les versets en trois étapes pour surmonter les obstacles linguistiques</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/fr/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/fr/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>Quran Explorer est un outil gratuit d&amp;rsquo;analyse arabe du Coran, conçu spécifiquement pour aider les apprenants non natifs à surmonter les obstacles linguistiques. Il propose une analyse approfondie des versets (lexique, grammaire, contexte), une correspondance multilingue, une aide audio et une fonction de notes. En trois étapes – localiser les versets, obtenir l&amp;rsquo;analyse, sauvegarder et partager – les utilisateurs accèdent gratuitement à cet outil, facilitant ainsi une apprentissage sans barrières.</description></item><item><title>Quran Explorer — безкоштовний інструмент аналізу арабської мови Корану, три кроки глибокого розкладу тексу для подолання мовного бар'єру</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/uk/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/uk/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>Quran Explorer — безкоштовний інструмент аналізу арабської мови Корану, створений для подолання мовних бар&amp;rsquo;єрів у навчанні для носіїв інших мов. Підтримує глибокий аналіз тексу (лексика, граматика, контекст), багатомовний порівняльний аналіз, аудіо-допомогу та функцію нотаток. Користувачі можуть безкоштовно скористатися послугами за три кроки визначення тексу, отримання аналізу, збереження/поділу, що спрощує навчання для початківців.</description></item><item><title>Quran Explorer — бесплатный инструмент анализа арабского Корана, три шага для глубокого понимания текста, преодоление языковых барьеров</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ru/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ru/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>Quran Explorer — бесплатный инструмент анализа арабского текста Корана, созданный для преодоления языковых барьеров при изучении священного текста не носителями языка. Предоставляет глубокий анализ текста (лексика, грамматика, исторический контекст), многоязычное сравнение, аудио-сопровождение и функцию заметок. Пользователь может бесплатно использовать инструмент за три простых шага определить текст, получить анализ, сохранить и поделиться. Это делает изучение Корана доступным для всех.</description></item><item><title>Quran Explorer Herramienta gratuita de análisis árabe del Corán, desglose profundo en tres pasos para superar barreras lingüísticas</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/es/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/es/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>Quran Explorer es una herramienta gratuita de análisis del árabe del Corán, diseñada específicamente para resolver las barreras lingüísticas en el estudio de los versículos por parte de no hablantes nativos. Ofrece análisis profundo de los versículos (incluyendo vocabulario, gramática y contexto), comparación multilingüe, ayuda con audio y función de notas. Los usuarios pueden utilizarla gratuitamente en tres pasos localizar el versículo, obtener el análisis y guardar/compartir, facilitando un aprendizaje accesible para todos.</description></item><item><title>quran explorer——免費《古蘭經》阿拉伯語解析工具，三步深度解析經文，輕鬆突破語言障礙</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>quran explorer是一款免費的《古蘭經》阿拉伯語解析工具，專為解決非母語者學習經文的語言障礙設計。支援經文深度解析（含詞彙、語法、背景）、多語對照、音頻輔助及筆記功能，使用者透過定位經文、獲取解析、保存分享三步即可免費使用，助力零門檻學習。</description></item><item><title>quran explorer：免费《古兰经》阿拉伯语解析工具，三步深度解构经文，轻松突破语言障碍</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:57:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/posts/1965dc6fabd8ba00aa03ad0dc132ae8f/</guid><description>quran explorer是一款免费的《古兰经》阿拉伯语解析工具，专为解决非母语者学习经文的语言障碍设计。支持经文深度解析（含词汇、语法、背景）、多语言对照、音频辅助及笔记功能，用户通过定位经文、获取解析、保存分享三步即可免费使用，助力零门槛学习。</description></item></channel></rss>