<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RAID on cmdragon's Blog</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/RAID/</link><description>Recent content in RAID on cmdragon's Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/RAID/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>¿Qué significa RAID? De los conceptos básicos a la configuración práctica esta herramienta calculadora te ayuda a empezar</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/es/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/es/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID (matriz de discos) combina múltiples discos para garantizar seguridad de datos, ampliar capacidad o mejorar rendimiento. Los diferentes niveles producen resultados muy distintos. Los principiantes deben definir sus necesidades, calcular capacidad y rendimiento, y seleccionar el software adecuado. Se recomienda una calculadora de almacenamiento RAID introduce parámetros para generar informes de configuración, ayudando a los principiantes a dominar rápidamente la selección de capacidad y nivel, evitando errores en la configuración.</description></item><item><title>Cosa significa RAID? Dalle basi alla configurazione pratica, questo strumento calcolatore ti aiuta a iniziare facilmente</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/it/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/it/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID (array di dischi) combina dischi multipli per garantire sicurezza dati, espansione capacità o miglioramento delle prestazioni. Le differenze tra i livelli sono significative. Per i principianti, è fondamentale definire le esigenze, calcolare capacità e prestazioni, e scegliere il software giusto. Si consiglia il calcolatore RAID per archiviazione inserendo i parametri, genera una relazione di configurazione per aiutare i nuovi utenti a scegliere rapidamente capacità e livelli RAID, evitando errori di configurazione.</description></item><item><title>Kas yra RAID? Nuo pagrindų iki praktinės konfigūracijos – šis skaičiuoklė padeda lengvai pradėti</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/lt/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/lt/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID (diskų masyvas) naudoja kelių diskų sąjungą, kad užtikrintų duomenų saugumą, plėstrą arba našumą. Skirtingos lygio savybės labai skiriasi. Pradedantiesiems konfigūruojant RAID reikia aiškiai nustatyti poreikius, apskaičiuoti talpą ir našumą, bei pasirinkti tinkamą programinę įrangą. Rekomenduojama RAID saugyklos skaičiuoklė, kuri įvedus parametrus generuoja konfigūracijos ataskaitą, padedanti pradedančiųjų greitai suprasti talpos ir lygio pasirinkimą, išvengdama klaidingos konfigūracijos.</description></item><item><title>O que significa RAID? Da concepção básica à configuração prática, esta ferramenta de cálculo facilita a sua aprendizagem</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/pt/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/pt/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID (Array de Discos Independentes) combina múltiplos discos para garantir segurança de dados, expandir capacidade ou melhorar desempenho. Diferentes níveis apresentam resultados distintos. Novatos devem definir necessidades, calcular capacidade/desempenho e escolher software adequado. Recomendamos a calculadora de armazenamento RAID, que gera relatórios de configuração ao inserir parâmetros, ajudando iniciantes a dominar rapidamente a escolha de nível e capacidade, evitando erros de configuração.</description></item><item><title>Qu'est-ce que RAID ? De la théorie à la configuration pratique, cet outil de calcul vous aide à maîtriser facilement</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/fr/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/fr/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID (matrice de disques) permet d&amp;rsquo;assurer la sécurité des données, d&amp;rsquo;élargir la capacité ou d&amp;rsquo;améliorer les performances grâce à l&amp;rsquo;association de plusieurs disques. Les différents niveaux offrent des résultats très variés. Un débutant doit clarifier ses besoins, calculer la capacité et les performances, et choisir un logiciel adapté. Nous recommandons un calculateur RAID, qui génère un rapport de configuration après saisie des paramètres, aidant les débutants à maîtriser rapidement le choix de la capacité et du niveau, évitant les erreurs de configuration.</description></item><item><title>RAID nedir? Temel kavramlardan uygulamalı yapılandırmaya kadar, bu hesaplayıcı aracıyla kolayca başlayın</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tr/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tr/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID (disk matrisi), birden fazla sabit disk kullanarak veri güvenliği, kapasite genişletme veya performans artışı sağlar. Farklı seviyelerin etkileri büyük ölçüde değişir. Yeni başlayanlar için yapılandırma yaparken ihtiyaçları netleştirilmeli, kapasite performans hesaplanmalı ve uygun yazılım seçilmelidir. RAID depolama hesaplayıcısı önerilir; parametreleri girerek yapılandırma raporu üretebilir, yeni başlayanların kapasite ve seviye seçimi konusunda hızlıca yetişmesini sağlar, yapılandırma hatalarını önler.</description></item><item><title>RAID 是什么意思啊？从基础概念到实操配置，这款计算器工具让你轻松上手</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/el/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/el/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID (πίνακας δίσκων) επιτυγχάνει ασφάλεια δεδομένων, επέκταση χωρητικότητας ή βελτίωση απόδοσης μέσω συνδυασμού πολλών δίσκων. Οι διαφορές μεταξύ των επιπέδων είναι σημαντικές. Οι αρχάριοι πρέπει να καθορίσουν τις ανάγκες τους, υπολογίσουν χωρητικότητα/απόδοση και επιλέξουν το σωστό λογισμικό. Συνιστάται ο υπολογιστής RAID, ο οποίος εισάγοντας παραμέτρους παράγει αναφορά διαμόρφωσης, βοηθώντας τους αρχάριους να επιλέξουν γρήγορα τη χωρητικότητα και το επίπεδο RAID, αποφεύγοντας λάθη διαμόρφωσης.</description></item><item><title>RAID 是什么意思啊？从基础概念到实操配置，这款计算器工具让你轻松上手</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID（磁盘阵列）通过多硬盘组合实现数据安全、容量扩展或性能提升，不同级别效果差异大。新手配置需明确需求、计算容量性能、选对软件。推荐RAID存储计算器，输入参数生成配置报告，助新手快速掌握容量与级别选择，避免配置错误。</description></item><item><title>RAID 是什麼意思啊？從基礎概念到實操配置，這款計算器工具讓你輕鬆上手</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/zh-tw/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/zh-tw/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID（磁碟陣列）透過多磁碟組合實現資料安全、容量擴展或效能提升，不同等級效果差異大。新手配置需明確需求、計算容量效能、選對軟體。推薦 RAID 儲存計算器，輸入參數產生配置報告，助新手快速掌握容量與等級選擇，避免配置錯誤。</description></item><item><title>RAID란 무엇인가요? 기초 개념부터 실전 구성까지, 이 계산기 도구로 쉽게 시작하세요</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ko/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ko/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID(디스크 어레이)는 다수의 하드디스크를 조합하여 데이터 안정성, 용량 확장, 성능 향상을 달성합니다. 각 레벨별 효과는 상당히 다릅니다. 초보자 구성 시 요구사항 명확화, 용량·성능 계산, 적절한 소프트웨어 선택이 필수적입니다. RAID 저장 계산기 도구를 추천하며, 파라미터 입력 후 구성 보고서를 생성해 초보자가 용량 및 레벨 선택을 신속히 습득하고 구성 오류를 방지할 수 있습니다.</description></item><item><title>RAIDとは何ですか？基礎概念から実践設定まで、この計算ツールで簡単に習得</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ja/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ja/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID（ディスクアレイ）は複数のハードディスクを組み合わせてデータセキュリティ、容量拡張、性能向上を実現します。レベルごとの効果は大きく異なります。初心者が設定する際は、ニーズの明確化、容量・性能の計算、適切なソフトウェアの選択が重要です。RAIDストレージ計算ツールを活用すれば、パラメータを入力するだけで設定レポートを生成し、容量とレベルの選択を迅速に習得できます。設定ミスを防ぎます。</description></item><item><title>Was bedeutet RAID? Von Grundlagen bis zur praktischen Konfiguration – dieser Rechner hilft Ihnen bei der Einrichtung</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/de/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/de/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID (Festplattenspeicherarray) ermöglicht durch Kombination mehrerer Festplatten Datensicherheit, Kapazitätsausweitung oder Leistungssteigerung. Die Effekte unterscheiden sich je nach Stufe. Für Anfänger ist es entscheidend, Anforderungen zu klären, Kapazität und Leistung zu berechnen und die richtige Software auszuwählen. Wir empfehlen einen spezialisierten RAID-Speicherrechner, der Konfigurationsberichte basierend auf Eingabewerten erstellt und Anfängern dabei hilft, Kapazität und Stufe präzise auszuwählen – ohne Konfigurationsfehler.</description></item><item><title>Wat betekent RAID? Van basisconcepten tot praktische configuratie – deze calculator helpt u gemakkelijk aan de slag</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/nl/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/nl/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID (schijfarray) verbindt meerdere harde schijven om gegevensveiligheid, capaciteitsuitbreiding of prestatieverbetering te bereiken. Verschillende niveaus hebben verschillende effecten. Beginners moeten eerst hun behoeften duidelijk maken, capaciteit en prestaties berekenen, en de juiste software kiezen. We raden een RAID-opslagcalculator aan vul parameters in om een configuratierapport te genereren, zodat beginners snel de juiste keuze maken voor capaciteit en niveau, en fouten bij configuratie voorkomen.</description></item><item><title>What Does RAID Mean? From Basic Concepts to Hands-On Configuration This Calculator Tool Makes It Easy</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID (Redundant Array of Independent Disks) combines multiple hard drives to enhance data security, expand capacity, or improve performance. Different RAID levels yield significantly varied results. Beginners need to clarify requirements, calculate capacity and performance, and select the right software. Recommended a RAID storage calculator that generates configuration reports based on input parameters, helping newcomers quickly master capacity and level selection while avoiding configuration errors.</description></item><item><title>Что означает RAID? От базовых понятий до практической настройки этот калькулятор поможет вам легко освоить тему</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ru/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ru/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID (массив дисков) обеспечивает безопасность данных, расширение объема и повышение производительности за счет объединения нескольких дисков. Разные уровни RAID имеют существенные различия в результатах. Новичкам при настройке необходимо четко определить потребности, рассчитать объем и производительность, выбрать подходящее ПО. Рекомендуется калькулятор RAID-массивов введите параметры, получите отчет по настройке, быстро освойте выбор объема и уровня, избегая ошибок конфигурации.</description></item><item><title>Що означає RAID? Від основ до практичної налаштування цей калькулятор допоможе вам легко оволодіти</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/uk/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/uk/posts/434552ebcdbd2984e886062543058346/</guid><description>RAID (масив дисків) дозволяє забезпечити безпеку даних, розширити місткість або покращити продуктивність за рахунок поєднання кількох дисків. Відмінності між рівнями RAID дуже впливають на результат. Початківцям важливо чітко визначити потреби, розрахувати місткість та продуктивність, а також обрати правильний софіт. Рекомендуємо використовувати RAID-калькулятор для зберігання введіть параметри, отримайте звіт із налаштуваннями, щоб швидко оволодіти вибором рівня та місткості без помилок.</description></item></channel></rss>