<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Snapdrop on cmdragon's Blog</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/Snapdrop/</link><description>Recent content in Snapdrop on cmdragon's Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/Snapdrop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guía de uso de Snapdrop Transfiere archivos entre teléfono y ordenador en tres pasos, sin interrupciones, seguro y eficiente</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/es/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/es/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Snapdrop es una herramienta de transferencia de archivos entre dispositivos sin necesidad de instalar clientes, resolviendo problemas como la lentitud de Bluetooth, límites de tamaño de archivo y la complicación de usar cables. Basado en una interfaz web, detecta automáticamente dispositivos en la misma red local, transfiere archivos de forma local sin almacenamiento en la nube, es seguro y eficiente, y admite múltiples formatos. Su funcionamiento es sencillo ambos dispositivos acceden al sitio web en la misma red WiFi, hacen clic en el dispositivo para enviar archivos y confirman el guardado. Tras la transferencia, no queda ningún residuo.</description></item><item><title>Guia de Utilização do Snapdrop Transfira Ficheiros Sem Fio Entre Telemóvel e Computador em 3 Passos, Seguro e Eficiente</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/pt/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/pt/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Snapdrop é uma ferramenta de transferência de ficheiros entre dispositivos sem necessidade de instalar clientes, resolvendo problemas como velocidade lenta do Bluetooth, limitações de tamanho e a complexidade de cabos. Baseado em interface web, descobre automaticamente dispositivos na mesma rede local, transfere ficheiros diretamente entre dispositivos locais sem armazenamento em nuvem, é seguro, eficiente e suporta vários formatos. Operação simples ambos os dispositivos acessam o site na mesma rede WiFi, clicam no dispositivo para enviar ficheiros e confirmam o salvamento. Após a transferência, não há resíduos.</description></item><item><title>Guida all'uso di Snapdrop Trasferisci file tra smartphone e computer in tre semplici passaggi, sicuro ed efficiente senza limitazioni</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/it/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/it/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Snapdrop è uno strumento di trasferimento file tra dispositivi senza bisogno di installare client, risolvendo problemi come la lentezza del Bluetooth, i limiti di dimensione e la complicazione dei cavi dati. Basato su una piattaforma web, rileva automaticamente i dispositivi nella stessa rete locale, trasferisce i file direttamente in locale senza archiviazione su cloud, offrendo una soluzione sicura, efficiente e supportante diversi formati. Operazione semplice entrambi i dispositivi collegati alla stessa rete WiFi visitano il sito web, cliccano sul dispositivo per trasferire i file, il destinatario conferma il salvataggio, e dopo il trasferimento non rimangono residui.</description></item><item><title>Guide d'utilisation de Snapdrop Transfert de fichiers sans heurt entre téléphone et ordinateur en trois étapes, sécurisé et efficace</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/fr/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/fr/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Snapdrop est un outil de transfert de fichiers entre appareils sans nécessiter d&amp;rsquo;installation client, résolvant les problèmes de lenteur du Bluetooth, des limites de taille des fichiers et des câbles USB encombrants. Basé sur une interface web, il détecte automatiquement les appareils connectés au même réseau local, transfère les fichiers localement sans stockage cloud, offrant sécurité et efficacité tout en supportant de nombreux formats de fichiers. Opération simple accédez au site web depuis le téléphone et l&amp;rsquo;ordinateur sur le même Wi-Fi, cliquez sur l&amp;rsquo;appareil cible pour envoyer le fichier, confirmez l&amp;rsquo;enregistrement côté réception. Aucun fichier résiduel après le transfert.</description></item><item><title>Snapdrop Gebruiksgids Drie Stappen voor Naadloze Bestandsverzending tussen Telefoon en Computer, Veilig en Efficiënt</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/nl/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/nl/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Snapdrop is een bestandsverzendtool tussen apparaten zonder client-installatie, die problemen zoals trage Bluetooth, bestandsgroottebeperkingen en onhandige kabels oplost. Gebaseerd op een webinterface, detecteert het automatisch apparaten in hetzelfde lokale netwerk, verzendt lokaal zonder cloudopslag, veilig en efficiënt, en ondersteunt meerdere bestandsformaten. Gebruik is eenvoudig beide apparaten openen dezelfde WiFi, bezoeken de website, klikken op het apparaat om bestanden te verzenden, ontvangende partij bevestigt opslag. Na afloop blijft er geen restant over.</description></item><item><title>Snapdrop Guide Transfer Files Between Phone and Computer Seamlessly in Three Steps – Secure, Efficient, and Unrestricted</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Snapdrop is a cross-device file transfer tool that requires no client installation, solving issues like slow Bluetooth transfers, file size limits on apps, and cumbersome cable connections. Built on a web interface, it automatically detects devices on the same local network, transfers files locally without cloud storage, ensuring security, efficiency, and support for multiple file formats. Simple operation both devices access the official site via the same Wi-Fi, click to send files, confirm save on the receiver, and leave no residual files after transfer.</description></item><item><title>Snapdrop Kullanım Kılavuzu Telefon ve Bilgisayar Arasında Süreksiz Dosya Aktarımı, Güvenli ve Sınırsız</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tr/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tr/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>snapdrop, istemci kurulumu gerektirmeyen çapraz cihaz dosya aktarım aracıdır. Bluetooth hızı yılan kadar yavaş, WeChat/QQ üzerinden dosya gönderirken boyut sınırlamaları, USB kablosu kullanmanın karmaşası gibi sorunları çözer. Web tabanlı olarak çalışır, aynı yerel ağda otomatik olarak cihazları keşfederek, bulut depolama olmadan yerel olarak aktarım yapar. Güvenli, verimli ve çoklu dosya biçimi desteği sunar. Kullanımı basit Aynı WiFi&amp;rsquo;de iki cihaz resmi sitesini ziyaret eder, cihazları seçip dosya gönderir, alıcı onaylar ve aktarım tamamlandıktan sonra hiçbir kalıntı bırakmaz.</description></item><item><title>Snapdrop naudojimo vadovas 3 žingsniai, kad lengvai perduotumėte failus tarp mobilaus įrenginio ir kompiuterio, saugiai ir efektyviai</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/lt/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/lt/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Snapdrop yra įrankis failų perdavimui tarp įrenginių be kliento programos įdiegimo, išspręsdamas problemą su lėtu Bluetooth, failų dydžio ribojimais ir duomenų laidų naudojimu. Remiantis naršyklės versija, įrenginiai automatiškai aptinkami vienoje lokaliame tinkle, failai perduodami tiesiogiai tarp įrenginių, be debesų saugyklos, saugiai ir efektyviai, palaikant įvairius failų formatus. Veikimas paprastas abu įrenginiai, esant vienai WiFi tinklo, apsilankant oficialioje svetainėje, spustelėjus įrenginį, siųsdami failą, gavėjas patvirtina išsaugojimą, po perdavimo failų likutis nebelieka.</description></item><item><title>Snapdrop 사용 가이드 3단계로 스마트폰과 컴퓨터 간 파일 무제한 전송, 안전하고 효율적</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ko/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ko/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Snapdrop은 클라이언트 설치 없이 크로스 기기 파일 전송이 가능한 도구로, 블루투스 속도 저하, 전송 용량 제한, 데이터 케이블 사용의 번거로움을 해결합니다. 웹 기반으로 동일한 로컬 네트워크 내에서 자동으로 장치를 발견하며, 클라우드 저장소를 사용하지 않고 로컬에서 직접 전송되어 안전하고 효율적이며, 다양한 파일 형식을 지원합니다. 사용법은 간단합니다. 동일한 WiFi 환경에서 양측이 공식 웹사이트에 접속한 후 장치를 선택해 파일을 전송하고, 수신자가 확인해 저장하면 됩니다. 전송 후 잔여 파일이 남지 않습니다.</description></item><item><title>Snapdrop-Anleitung Dateien nahtlos zwischen Smartphone und Computer übertragen – sicher, effizient und ohne Einschränkungen</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/de/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/de/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Snapdrop ist ein clientloses Werkzeug zur Dateiübertragung zwischen Geräten, das Probleme wie langsame Bluetooth-Übertragungen, Dateigrößenbeschränkungen und das Verwenden von Datenkabeln löst. Basierend auf einer Webanwendung erkennt es automatisch Geräte im selben lokalen Netzwerk (LAN), überträgt Dateien direkt zwischen Geräten ohne Cloud-Speicherung, ist sicher, effizient und unterstützt verschiedene Dateiformate. Die Bedienung ist einfach Beide Geräte müssen im selben WLAN sein, die Website besuchen, auf das Gerät klicken und die Datei übertragen. Der Empfänger bestätigt die Speicherung. Nach Abschluss bleibt keine Datei gespeichert.</description></item><item><title>Snapdrop使用ガイド：3ステップでスマホとパソコン間のファイルをスムーズに転送、安全で制限なし</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ja/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ja/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Snapdropはクライアントのインストール不要で、複数デバイス間のファイル転送を実現するツールです。Bluetoothの遅さやファイルサイズ制限、データケーブルの煩わしさを解消します。ウェブブラウザベースで、同一ローカルネットワーク内に自動でデバイスを検出し、クラウド経由なしのローカル転送を実現。プライバシー保護と高速性を両立し、さまざまなファイル形式をサポートしています。操作はシンプル：同一WiFi下で双方が公式サイトにアクセスし、デバイスを選択してファイルを送信、受信側が保存を確認するだけ。転送後はファイルが残らないため、安全かつスムーズです。</description></item><item><title>Snapdrop使用指南：三步实现手机与电脑无缝文件传输，安全高效无限制</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>snapdrop是无需安装客户端的跨设备文件传输工具，解决蓝牙慢、传输限大小、数据线繁琐等问题。基于网页端，同一局域网自动发现设备，本地传输无云存储，安全高效，支持多格式文件。操作简单：同WiFi下双方访问官网，点击设备传文件，接收方确认保存，传输后无残留。</description></item><item><title>Snapdrop使用指南：三步實現手機與電腦無縫檔案傳輸，安全高效無限制</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/zh-tw/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/zh-tw/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>snapdrop是無需安裝客戶端的跨裝置檔案傳輸工具，解決藍牙慢、傳輸限大小、數據線繁瑣等問題。基於網頁端，同一區域網路自動偵測裝置，本地傳輸無雲端儲存，安全高效，支援多格式檔案。操作簡單：同WiFi下雙方訪問官網，點擊裝置傳檔案，接收端確認儲存，傳輸後無殘留。</description></item><item><title>Οδηγός χρήσης του Snapdrop Τρία βήματα για ασύγκριτη μεταφορά αρχείων μεταξύ κινητού και υπολογιστή, ασφαλής, αποτελεσματικός και χωρίς περιορισμούς</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/el/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/el/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Το Snapdrop είναι εργαλείο μεταφοράς αρχείων μεταξύ συσκευών, χωρίς ανάγκη εγκατάστασης πελάτη, που λύνει τα προβλήματα της αργής μεταφοράς μέσω Bluetooth, των περιορισμένων μεγεθών αρχείων και της περίπλοκης σύνδεσης με καλώδιο. Λειτουργεί ως ιστοσελίδα, ανακαλύπτει αυτόματα τις συσκευές στο ίδιο τοπικό δίκτυο, μεταφέρει τα αρχεία τοπικά χωρίς αποθήκευση στο cloud, είναι ασφαλές και αποτελεσματικό, και υποστηρίζει πολλά είδη αρχείων. Η χρήση είναι απλή οι δύο συσκευές πρέπει να βρίσκονται στο ίδιο Wi-Fi, να επισκεφθούν την ιστοσελίδα, να κάνουν κλικ στη συσκευή για μεταφορά, ο λήπτης επιβεβαιώνει την αποθήκευση, και μετά τη μεταφορά δεν απομένουν κατάλοιπα.</description></item><item><title>Посібник з використання Snapdrop три кроки для безперервної передачі файлів між телефоном і комп'ютером, безпечна та ефективна без обмежень</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/uk/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/uk/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Snapdrop — це інструмент для передачі файлів між пристроями без необхідності встановлення клієнта, який вирішує проблеми повільної передачі через Bluetooth, обмежень на розмір файлів та складності з кабелем. Він працює через веб-інтерфейс, автоматично виявляє пристрої в одній місцевій мережі, передає файли без хмарного зберігання, є безпечним і ефективним, підтримує різні формати. Простота використання обидва пристрої в одній мережі Wi-Fi відвідують офіційний сайт, натискають на пристрій для передачі файлів, отримувач підтверджує збереження. Після передачі файлів залишків немає.</description></item><item><title>Руководство по использованию Snapdrop три простых шага для бесшовной передачи файлов между телефоном и компьютером, безопасно и эффективно без ограничений</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ru/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ru/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Snapdrop — это инструмент передачи файлов между устройствами без установки приложения, решающий проблемы медленной передачи через Bluetooth, ограничения размера файлов и неудобства использования кабеля. Основанный на веб-интерфейсе, он автоматически обнаруживает устройства в локальной сети, передает данные напрямую без облачного хранения, обеспечивая безопасность и эффективность. Поддерживает различные форматы файлов. Простота использования оба устройства в одной сети Wi-Fi открывают официальный сайт, нажимают на устройство для передачи, получатель подтверждает сохранение — после передачи файлы не остаются на устройствах.</description></item><item><title>دليل استخدام Snapdrop ثلاث خطوات لتحقيق نقل الملفات السلس بين الهاتف والكمبيوتر، آمن وفعال دون قيود</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ar/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ar/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://blog.cmdragon.cn/images/6fd6463271834f2c905d01c5349000c2~tplv-5jbd59dj06-image.png" alt="cover.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;عندما تحاول نقل ملفات بين الهاتف والكمبيوتر، هل واجهتك مشكلة مثل سرعة نقل البلوتوث البطيئة، أو قيود حجم الملفات عند استخدام واتساب/QQ، أو التعقيد الناتج عن استخدام الكابلات؟ في الواقع، أداة نقل الملفات بين الأجهزة المُسمَّاة Snapdrop (&lt;a href="https://tools.cmdragon.cn/zh/apps/snapdrop"&gt;https://tools.cmdragon.cn/zh/apps/snapdrop&lt;/a&gt;) تُحل جميع هذه المشاكل. فهي تتيح نقل الملفات السلس بين الهاتف والكمبيوتر دون الحاجة إلى تثبيت تطبيق عميل، فقط عبر المتصفح، مع عملية بسيطة وأمان عالي وكفاءة، مما يجعلها خيارًا مثاليًّا لنقل الصور والمستندات والفيديوهات في المواقف اليومية مثل العمل أو الحياة الشخصية.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>