<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Visualization on cmdragon's Blog</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/data-visualization/</link><description>Recent content in Data Visualization on cmdragon's Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 01:53:29 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/data-visualization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Complete Guide to Lucky Draw Feature - Practical Guide from Configuration to Data Tracking, Easily Boost Event Participation</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en-US/posts/789a8a96d0b29c756c16823940badd90/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 01:53:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en-US/posts/789a8a96d0b29c756c16823940badd90/</guid><description>Lucky Draw is a professional lottery tool with core features including custom weight control, real-time data statistics dashboard, multi-scenario adaptability (live streaming, annual meetings, marketing, etc.), Excel batch import, and multi-language support, meeting cross-border event needs. Suitable for live streaming interaction, corporate events, marketing promotions, and other scenarios, operations cover creating activities, setting rules, starting lottery, and exporting results, enabling efficient and controllable lottery activities.</description></item><item><title>Struggling with Graph TD Table Data Visualization? Mermaid Live Editor Offers Real-Time Preview + User-Friendly Syntax for Professional Flowcharts/Progress Charts</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/4e39beda336567fcc19d7569bcec9c9e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 10:55:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/4e39beda336567fcc19d7569bcec9c9e/</guid><description>Traditional table-to-chart conversion suffers from complex manual operations, poor format compatibility, and insufficient real-time feedback. Mermaid Live Editor supports Graph TD syntax, enabling real-time flowchart generation and preview, drag-and-drop styling adjustments, and multi-format export (PNG/SVG), ideal for project management and technical documentation.</description></item></channel></rss>