<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cross-Device-Sharing on cmdragon's Blog</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/Cross-Device-Sharing/</link><description>Recent content in Cross-Device-Sharing on cmdragon's Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/Cross-Device-Sharing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/de/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/de/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online ist ein Open-Source-Peer-to-Peer-Übertragungstool, das ohne Registrierung, Konfiguration oder Installation über den Browser direkt genutzt werden kann. Es unterstützt die sofortige Freigabe von Bildern, Videos, PDFs und Links. Geräte werden automatisch über das gleiche Netzwerk erkannt, Inhalte werden ausgewählt und der Empfang bestätigt – ideal für Notfalltransfers und Gruppenaktivitäten.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online is an open-source peer-to-peer transfer tool that doesn&amp;rsquo;t require registration, setup, or installation; it can be used directly by accessing it through a browser. It supports instant sharing of images, videos, PDFs, and links, and devices automatically identify each other on the same network. It&amp;rsquo;s suitable for urgent file transfers, group sharing, etc., and is safe and efficient.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/nl/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/nl/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online is een open-source peer-to-peer transfertool die zonder registratie, instellingen of installatie via een browser direct te gebruiken is. Het ondersteunt het onmiddellijk delen van afbeeldingen, video’s, PDF’s en links. Apparaten herkennen elkaar automatisch op hetzelfde netwerk, je selecteert de inhoud en bevestigt de ontvangst, ideaal voor het snelle overbrengen van bestanden, het delen tijdens bijeenkomsten, etc. Het is veilig en efficiënt.</description></item></channel></rss>