<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cross-Device File Transfer on cmdragon's Blog</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/Cross-device-File-Transfer/</link><description>Recent content in Cross-Device File Transfer on cmdragon's Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 14:06:09 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/Cross-device-File-Transfer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recommended Free Online Tool for Cross-Device File Transfer Between Phones and Computers – No Installation, Secure Encryption, Instant Use, Overcoming Traditional Transfer Pain Points!</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/02b6f4f156160f95841591e855b62484/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 14:06:09 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/02b6f4f156160f95841591e855b62484/</guid><description>Cross-device file transfer between smartphones and computers has become essential, yet traditional methods face limitations from version compatibility, privacy concerns, or costs. Free online tools like &lt;a href="https://tools.cmdragon.cn/apps/snapdrop"&gt;this web-based solution&lt;/a&gt; enable direct file transfers without installation, support multiple formats, and encrypt data throughout transmission. Pair devices via QR code or verification code for simple, instant use. No registration required—ideal for temporary transfers or high-privacy scenarios, boosting efficiency while safeguarding data security.</description></item><item><title>Snapdrop Guide Transfer Files Between Phone and Computer Seamlessly in Three Steps – Secure, Efficient, and Unrestricted</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/ff09bf3567c37a0a1450ba925ff96b84/</guid><description>Snapdrop is a cross-device file transfer tool that requires no client installation, solving issues like slow Bluetooth transfers, file size limits on apps, and cumbersome cable connections. Built on a web interface, it automatically detects devices on the same local network, transfers files locally without cloud storage, ensuring security, efficiency, and support for multiple file formats. Simple operation both devices access the official site via the same Wi-Fi, click to send files, confirm save on the receiver, and leave no residual files after transfer.</description></item></channel></rss>