<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Snapdrop Online on cmdragon's Blog</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/snapdrop-online/</link><description>Recent content in Snapdrop Online on cmdragon's Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/snapdrop-online/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ar/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ar/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online هو أداة لنقل الملفات المباشر مفتوحة المصدر، ولا تتطلب تسجيل أو إعداد أو تثبيت، ويمكن استخدامها مباشرةً من خلال متصفح الويب، وتدعم مشاركة الصور ومقاطع الفيديو وملفات PDF والروابط بشكل فوري. يتم التعرف على الأجهزة المتصلة بنفس الشبكة، واختيار المحتوى وتأكيده، مما يجعلها مثالية لنقل الملفات العاجلة ومشاركة الملفات في المناسبات، وآمنة وفعالة.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/de/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/de/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online ist ein Open-Source-Peer-to-Peer-Übertragungstool, das ohne Registrierung, Konfiguration oder Installation über den Browser direkt genutzt werden kann. Es unterstützt die sofortige Freigabe von Bildern, Videos, PDFs und Links. Geräte werden automatisch über das gleiche Netzwerk erkannt, Inhalte werden ausgewählt und der Empfang bestätigt – ideal für Notfalltransfers und Gruppenaktivitäten.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/el/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/el/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online είναι ένα ανοιχτού κώδικα εργαλείο αμοιβαίας μεταφοράς αρχείων, χωρίς εγγραφή, ρύθμιση ή εγκατάσταση, που μπορεί να χρησιμοποιηθεί απευθείας μέσω του browser, υποστηρίζοντας την άμεση κοινή χρήση εικόνων, βίντεο, PDF και συνδέσμων. Τα συστήματα ανιχνεύουν αυτόματα συσκευές στο ίδιο δίκτυο, επιλέγοντας το περιεχόμενο και επιβεβαιώνοντας τη λήψη, κατάλληλο για επείγουσες μεταφορές αρχείων, κοινή χρήση σε συγκεντρώσεις κ.λπ., ασφαλές και αποτελεσματικό.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online is an open-source peer-to-peer transfer tool that doesn&amp;rsquo;t require registration, setup, or installation; it can be used directly by accessing it through a browser. It supports instant sharing of images, videos, PDFs, and links, and devices automatically identify each other on the same network. It&amp;rsquo;s suitable for urgent file transfers, group sharing, etc., and is safe and efficient.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/es/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/es/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online es una herramienta de transferencia punto a punto de código abierto, sin necesidad de registro, configuración o instalación, accesible directamente a través del navegador. Admite la compartición instantánea de imágenes, vídeos, PDF y enlaces. Los dispositivos se identifican automáticamente en la misma red, se selecciona el contenido y se confirma la recepción, lo que la hace adecuada para transferencias de archivos urgentes, compartir en reuniones, etc. Es segura y eficiente.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/it/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/it/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online è uno strumento open source di trasferimento P2P, che non richiede registrazione, configurazione o installazione basta accedere tramite browser per condividere immediatamente immagini, video, PDF e link. I dispositivi sulla stessa rete vengono rilevati automaticamente, selezionare il contenuto e confermare la ricezione completa il trasferimento. Ideale per trasferimenti di file urgenti, condivisioni in occasioni sociali e scenari in cui è richiesta una soluzione sicura ed efficiente.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ko/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ko/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online는 오픈소스 피어 투 피어(Peer-to-Peer) 전송 도구로, 등록, 설정, 설치 없이 브라우저에서 직접 접근하여 사용할 수 있습니다. 즉시 이미지, 영상, PDF 및 링크를 공유할 수 있으며, 같은 네트워크 내 장치는 자동으로 인식하여 선택하고 수신을 확인하면 전송이 완료됩니다. 긴급 파일 전송, 모임 공유 등에서 안전하고 효율적이며, 사용이 필요할 때마다 손쉬운 접근이 가능합니다.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/lt/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/lt/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online yra atvirojo kodo taikymas, skirtas tiesioginiam failų perdavimui be registruotis, nustatyti ar įdiegti. Pakanka atidaryti naršyklėje, kad galėtumėte iš karto dalintis nuotraukomis, vaizdo įrašais, PDF failais ir nuorodomis. Įrenginiai, esantys vienoje tinklo srityje, automatiškai atpažįstami, pasirinkus turinį ir patvirtinus priėmimą, failas perduodamas iš karto. Šis įrankis puikiai tinka skubiam failų perdavimui, susirinkimų dalijimuisi ir kt., užtikrindamas saugumą ir efektyvumą.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/nl/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/nl/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online is een open-source peer-to-peer transfertool die zonder registratie, instellingen of installatie via een browser direct te gebruiken is. Het ondersteunt het onmiddellijk delen van afbeeldingen, video’s, PDF’s en links. Apparaten herkennen elkaar automatisch op hetzelfde netwerk, je selecteert de inhoud en bevestigt de ontvangst, ideaal voor het snelle overbrengen van bestanden, het delen tijdens bijeenkomsten, etc. Het is veilig en efficiënt.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/pt/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/pt/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online é uma ferramenta de transferência ponto a ponto de código aberto, sem necessidade de registo, configuração ou instalação. Basta aceder diretamente através do navegador para partilhar imagens, vídeos, PDFs e links em tempo real. Os dispositivos na mesma rede são automaticamente detetados, selecionando o conteúdo e confirmando a receção conclui a transferência. Ideal para transferências urgentes, partilha em reuniões e outros cenários, sendo segura e eficiente.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ru/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ru/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online是开源点对点传输工具，无需注册、设置或安装，浏览器直接访问即可使用，支持即时共享图片、视频、PDF及链接。设备同网自动识别，选择内容并确认接收即可完成传输，适用于紧急文件传输、聚会分享等场景，安全高效。</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/uk/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/uk/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online — це відкритий інструмент передачі файлів безпосередньо між пристроями (точка-точка), який не потребує реєстрації, налаштувань або встановлення. Його можна використовувати безпосередньо через браузер для миттєвого обміну зображеннями, відео, PDF-файлами та посиланнями. Пристрої в одній мережі Wi-Fi автоматично виявляються, достатньо обрати контент та підтвердити отримання — передача завершується миттєво. Ідеальний для екстрених передач, поділів на зустрічах та інших сценаріїв, безпечний та ефективний.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online是开源点对点传输工具，无需注册、设置或安装，浏览器直接访问即可使用，支持即时共享图片、视频、PDF及链接。设备同网自动识别，选择内容并确认接收即可完成传输，适用于紧急文件传输、聚会分享等场景，安全高效。</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/zh-tw/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/zh-tw/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online是开源點對點傳輸工具，無需註冊、設定或安裝，瀏覽器直接訪問即可使用，支援即時共享圖片、影片、PDF及連結。設備同網自動辨識，選擇內容並確認接收即可完成傳輸，適用於緊急文件傳輸、聚會分享等場景，安全高效。</description></item><item><title>Snapdrop online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/fr/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/fr/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop online est un outil de transmission peer-à-peer open source. Il ne nécessite aucune inscription, configuration ou installation, il suffit d&amp;rsquo;accéder via un navigateur web. Il permet un partage instantané d&amp;rsquo;images, de vidéos, de PDFs et de liens. Les appareils sur le même réseau sont automatiquement détectés. Une fois la sélection effectuée et la confirmation de réception, la transmission est effectuée. Il est idéal pour la transmission de fichiers urgents, le partage lors de réunions ou d&amp;rsquo;assemblées, offrant à la fois sécurité et efficacité.</description></item><item><title>Snapdrop Online</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tr/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tr/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>Snapdrop Online, açık kaynaklı uçtan uca dosya aktarım aracıdır. Kayıt, kurulum veya yükleme gerektirmez, tarayıcı üzerinden doğrudan erişimle kullanılır. Görsel, video, PDF ve bağlantıları anında paylaşmanıza olanak tanır. Aynı ağdaki cihazlar otomatik olarak algılanır, içerik seçip alıcı onayladığında aktarım tamamlanır. Acil dosya aktarımı, toplantıda paylaşım gibi senaryolarda güvenli ve verimli kullanılır.</description></item><item><title>snapdrop online（点対点（P2P）ファイル転送ツール）</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ja/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/ja/posts/83f41c2dcb5ca82f53afa9f93616945e/</guid><description>snapdrop onlineは、登録不要・設定不要・インストール不要の点対点（P2P）ファイル転送ツールです。ブラウザで直接アクセスすれば使用可能で、画像、動画、PDF、リンクを瞬時に共有できます。同一ネットワーク上のデバイスであれば自動で認識し、ファイルを選択して受け入れを確認するだけで転送完了。緊急時のファイル転送や集会での共有など、セキュリティと高効率を実現しています。</description></item></channel></rss>