<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mermaid-Syntax on cmdragon's Blog</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/Mermaid-Syntax/</link><description>Recent content in Mermaid-Syntax on cmdragon's Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:08:04 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.cmdragon.cn/tags/Mermaid-Syntax/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Für Einsteiger Empfehlung für kostenlose Flowchart-Tools – Textgenerierung ohne Lernkurve, in 3 Minuten startklar, dauerhaft kostenlos</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/de/posts/ed40415a58cc641eab9609637ded76c2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:08:04 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/de/posts/ed40415a58cc641eab9609637ded76c2/</guid><description>Einsteiger bei der Erstellung von Flussdiagrammen stoßen häufig auf komplexe Tools oder kostenpflichtige Lösungen. Dieser Artikel empfiehlt ein kostenloses Flowchart-Tool, das auf Mermaid-Syntax basiert. Mit einfachen Textbeschreibungen werden Diagramme generiert – ohne Registrierung, dauerhaft kostenlos und ideal für tägliche Planung oder Projektzusammenarbeit.</description></item><item><title>Must-Read for Flowchart Beginners! Top Free Flowchart Tools Recommended – Zero Learning Curve, Text-to-Diagram in 3 Minutes, Permanently Free</title><link>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/ed40415a58cc641eab9609637ded76c2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:08:04 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.cmdragon.cn/en/posts/ed40415a58cc641eab9609637ded76c2/</guid><description>Newcomers often struggle with complex tools or paid subscriptions when drawing flowcharts. This article recommends a free flowchart tool based on Mermaid syntax. Simply describe your process in text to generate diagrams instantly—no registration required, permanently free, and ideal for daily planning, project collaboration, and more. Perfect for beginners to effortlessly map out workflows.</description></item></channel></rss>